{
    "subject": "Suzy_Kendall",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Dudley_Moore",
    "human_readable": "Suzy Kendall is married to Dudley Moore.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9108328819274902,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Suzy Kendall and Dudley Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9018261432647705,
            "question": "Who is Suzy Kendall married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8967296481132507,
            "question": "Name a famous person who Suzy Kendall is married to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8726441860198975,
            "question": "Is Dudley Moore married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7583543062210083,
            "question": "What type of relationship do Suzy Kendall and Dudley Moore share?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5271689295768738,
            "question": "In what field are both Suzy Kendall and Dudley Moore known?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4515058696269989,
            "question": "Who is Dudley Moore known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10737452656030655,
            "question": "Are there any well-known actors who are married to each other?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0736488550901413,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a famous marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05999944731593132,
            "question": "Who are some notable couples in the entertainment industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Suzy Kendall is married to Dudley Moore.",
            "html": "yago_26157_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a famous marriage?",
            "html": "yago_26157_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any well-known actors who are married to each other?",
            "html": "yago_26157_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Dudley Moore known for?",
            "html": "yago_26157_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26157_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that Suzy Kendall and Dudley Moore were married from 1968 to 1972,  they are now divorced. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple. According to the text, Suzy Kendall was previously married to Dudley Moore (1968 - 1972). This indicates a marriage between the two individuals, confirming the correctness of the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Suzy Kendall was previously married to Dudley Moore from 1968 to 1972, and that they divorced. There is no information supporting that she is currently married to Dudley Moore."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"no\"}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several pieces of text state that Dudley Moore and Suzy Kendall divorced in 1972.  Additionally, information about their marriage being a secret ceremony followed by a later divorce is provided.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly states that Dudley Moore and Suzy Kendall were married from 1968 to 1972, and more recent information indicates that Suzy Kendall is currently possibly single.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}